http://royalrivercasino.com/privacy-policy

Entertainment
Please read the Privacy Policy of Royal River Casino (“we,” “our,” or “us”) carefully to learn about our information practices on our website www.royalrivercasino.com, and the choices you can make about the collection, use and disclosure of your information. The terms of our Privacy Policy apply to all users of our Website. If you do not agree with the terms of our Privacy Policy, you should immediately stop using our Website.Information we collect about youYou may voluntarily provide us with your personal information, including the following information: name, physical address, email address, phone number, birth date as well as any other information you voluntarily provide. If you make a purchase on our Website, we also will ask you for additional information, including the credit card number and expiration date, billing address, shipping address, name on the account and telephone numbers for the billing and shipping addresses.Our Web servers automatically identify the Internet Protocol addresses of each visitor, the type of browser used, the pages viewed and the website last visited before visiting our Website.How we use your informationWe may use your personal information for any of the following purposes:To understand the use of our Website and make improvementsTo fulfill prizesTo register visitors for online activities, including online ordering, sweepstakes, contests, surveys, employment applications, comment forms or any other online interactive activitiesTo respond to specific requests from visitorsTo protect the security or integrity of our Website if necessaryTo send newsletters and notices of special promotions, offers or solicitations through your selected opt-in methodsIn general, to promote and market our business and various products.In addition, from time to time, we may market certain third party services through our Website. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we will pass your relevant personal information, which may include your name, address and credit card information, to that third party.In addition, from time to time, we may market certain third party services through our Website. Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we will pass your relevant personal information, which may include your name, address and credit card information, to that third party.How we disclose your informationWe will not sell, rent, loan, transfer or otherwise disclose any personal information to third parties except as set forth in our Privacy Policy.We may share personal information with third parties under the following circumstances:In connection with a court order, subpoena, government investigation or when otherwise required by lawIn the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or similar eventWorking with third party companies to support the technical operation of our Website or execute a specific promotion or program (such as providing responses to the Contact Us page, conduct surveys, or maintain a database of visitor information, etc.)In connection with marketing certain third party services through our WebsiteWorking with third parties that provide services on our behalf and that may use the information solely in conjunction with the specific services they provide for us, including handling e-mail, processing credit card payments, administering sweepstakes, deploying surveys and handling guest complaints.Some of these third parties may be involved in administering or supplementing our databases and will need to have access to the information in order to do so. For example, we may retain a third party to verify the accuracy of information within our databases or to gather additional information about individuals within our databases from commercially available sources.AccessOur Website may allow you to choose to receive or stop receiving communications from us. You may opt out of email programs at any time by following the opt-out instructions provided in the email you receive.CookiesWe may use cookies, which are small files placed on your hard drive to identify you when you visit our Website. We use this technology to provide you with a more customized browsing experience. You may set your browser to refuse the cookies, but there may be pages on our Website that you will not be able to access if you do.Cookies also enable us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Website. Together with our ad management partner(s), we use this information to help us manage online advertising. The information collected by cookies does not contain personal information (for example, name, physical address or email address).We also utilize a third party to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from the customers of our Website to improve the quality of our Website. No data collected by a third party on our behalf may be owned or used by that third party.SecurityWe take reasonable security measures to protect personal information submitted by users from loss and misuse, but cannot guarantee that these measures will prevent a third party from circumventing them and unlawfully intercepting or accessing transmissions or private communications or where an error may occur in the administration of our Website. Some emails sent to or from our Website may not be secure. Please consider this when sending information to us by email. Accordingly, we recommend that you use caution whenever submitting personal information online.Links to other websitesOur Website may contain links to other websites that we may not own or operate. We neither can control nor are responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website that collects personally identifiable information. Our Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected on our Website.Policy changesWe may modify, alter or update our Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review our Privacy Policy frequently. We will not provide individual notice to you of changes to our Privacy Policy, but when we make updates to our Privacy Policy, we will update the date at the top of our Privacy Policy.How to contact usIf you have questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or regarding your privacy, please contact us using our Contact Form or by mail at:Royal River Casino 607 S. Veterans StreetFlandreau, SD 57028
